801-419-8593

# CORY

RESCHKE

reschkecm@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/coryreschke @coryreschke

#### BIOGRAPHY.

Over six years' experience consulting, analyzing & modeling business processes, and developing custom BPA solutions. Also, skilled in data and business analytics with a master's degree in business analytics from the University of Utah. Looking to pivot into a career in business intelligence and data analytics.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE.

#### PROFESSIONAL SERVICES ENGINEER

#### MetaSource

May 2011 - Present

- Maximize the efficiency of organizations by analyzing & automating business processes.
- Built a document classification model to identify over 100 different document types with 90% accuracy.
- Automated a process for a healthcare-staffing company that was previously performed manually by 140 employees.

#### ASSISTANT CHANGE MANAGER

Brigham Young University, Office of IT

May 2011 - May 2017

- Minimized risk to IT systems worldwide by working with a cross-functional team of business and technical personnel to review and authorize system changes.
- Led semi-weekly meetings of the change advisory board.
- Enforced change-management policies across multiple groups and teams

# EDUCATION.

#### MASTER OF SCIENCE, BUSINESS ANALYTICS

University of Utah David, Eccles School of Business

2015 - 2017

- Built predictive models for Intermountain Healthcare using patient-satisfaction survey data. The goal of the project was to improve care by incentivizing physicians based on patient satisfaction.
- Synthesized hospital charge data with cost of living index data. This data was studied to
  determine whether regional fluctuation in healthcare costs could be primarily attributed to
  differences in cost of living.
- Relevant coursework: Advanced Data Mining, Statistics & Predictive Analytics, Data
   Visualization, Text & Opinion Mining, Operations Strategy, Data Analysis & Decision Making.

#### BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, INFORMATION SYSTEMS

Brigham Young University, Marriott School of Management

2006 - 2011

 Relevant coursework: Systems Analysis, System Design & Implementation, Marketing Management, Business Strategy, Enterprise Application Development, Adv. Data Communications, Business Processes & Controls.

## SKILLS.

SOL

R

Data visualization

Interpersonal communication

Process modelling

Presentation & public speaking

# VOLUNTEER EXPERENCE.

UTAH MMHC System Administrator

Nov 2016 - Present

WOMEN TECH COUNCIL
Mentor

March 2016

#### LANGUAGES.

English (native)

French (fluent)

# INTERESTS.

Horsemanship

Fly fishing

Data science

Chess

Education